[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
"Kiss Or Kill"
(Episode 9)
He's not like us.
He won't stick around.
Relax.
We're not going to kill him anytime soon.
Maybe one day when you think of it,
you can use him for a little fun.
Whatever.
I got bored of him a long time ago.
I thought having him in our hands
was the only way to make
sure you were on my side.
How could he possibly
compare to the bond between us?
Besides,
we have mutual interests now.
I've been waiting for this day.
So all this time,
this is what you've been busy with.
You already know,
so why ask?
I could have helped you too.
Why did you go to him?
He's more useful than you.
He might help you kill Lin Cang today,
but tomorrow he'll put a knife
to your throat.
That's a problem for tomorrow.
Lin Yan,
you keep saying you want revenge,
and that you'll never become him.
But everything you're doing now,
isn't it exactly what he taught you?
That batch of samples,
you tampered with it to make the
Black Moon Syndicate suspicious,
so you could force Lin Cang to step down
and take his place legitimately.
Am I right?
So what if you are?
You promised me that
you wouldn't become him.
I am indeed different from him.
That's why I'm going to replace him.
You're ruthless now. What's the
difference between you and him?
Raising another batch
of killers to work for you?
What age are you going
to start picking them from?
Seven?
Is that too old?
If he can do it,
why can't I?
That's how I was raised.
I didn't have a choice before,
but now I do.
You could try to let it go
and live a clean life.
I don't care about that.
I want to take back what belongs to me.
I know
you approached me from the start
just to get something out of me.
But I actually kind of liked you,
so it doesn't matter.
But now,
you're in my way,
and I can't just let that slide.
Or you can choose to help me,
work with me.
We can do this together.
So,
you've been lying to me this whole time.
I'm helping you.
You're not that kind of person.
I've always been this way.
By the way,
this is Black Scorpion's turf.
You'd better behave.
Maybe you should think it through
and choose to rely on me.
It's handled?
He's not important.
You're pretty ruthless.
What's your next move?
Next,
we wait for Uncle to notify
us of the trade location.
No matter who transports the goods,
as long as we have the person,
we have leverage to negotiate.
You're quite the schemer.
Are you backing out?
I already agreed to work with you.
Once the goods arrive,
it's the end of the line for that old man.
Lin Yan,
you broke your promise.
But I can't.
Why is it here?
I followed the navigation
address Lin Cang left in the car.
Did he find out...?
Brothers,
I'll take you to see Daddy.
You have a dad?
Yeah.
Daddy told me to come pick you up.
Let's go.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
Daddy reminded me
to check if you guys
brought anything with you.
Brought what?
Bang, bang, bang!
Brother, you have something in your waist.
I saw it.
If you don't give it to
me, Daddy will be mad,
and he won't love me anymore.
Just give it to her.
I finished my mission!
Sister, I finished my mission!
Good job.
Daddy will like you.
Brother Yan, you're here.
That's the new orphan Daddy adopted.
He said he wanted to
give me a little sister.
Isn't she cute?
A-ren,
if you want to play,
you can come find me.
But,
Brother Yan, you're always busy.
But it's okay.
Now I have a little sister to play with.
Daddy has been waiting
for you for a long time.
Come on.
- Uncle.
A-ren,
go play with A-lian for a bit.
So,
do you remember this place?
Of course, Uncle.
We grew up here.
My parents
founded this orphanage.
My brother and sister-in-law
were truly good people.
It's a pity the good die young.
A-yan,
they entrusted you to me.
I would never harm you.
A-peng,
I raised you,
and I've always treated you
like my own flesh and blood.
Yes, Uncle.
And we
will always remember your kindness.
Uncle,
aren't we delivering the goods to
the Black Moon Syndicate today?
Are we making the trade here?
No rush.
They'll be here a bit later.
Let's play a game first.
I'm getting old.
I don't know
how you young people play these days.
But,
I should learn a thing or two.
A-peng, you know how.
You deal.
I wouldn't say learn.
We still rely on you to teach us, Uncle.
Since you're interested, Uncle,
I should keep you company.
So, what are we playing?
Whatever you say, Uncle.
I'm just afraid the old ways
won't appeal to you young folks.
They'll be replaced sooner or later.
You're joking, Uncle.
Only the classics
make it to the main table.
Alright.
Let's play Blackjack then.
You're the dealer, you deal.
Look at my memory.
I completely forgot.
I have to deal the cards.
I'll stand.
Hit me.
I'll have to trouble you
one more time, Uncle.
If you want it, I'll
naturally give it to you.
But you need to keep
track of your hole cards.
And know when it's right to hit.
You make a good point, Uncle.
Then I'm good here.
Fifteen is enough.
Blackjack.
You stand on seventeen.
You're too scared to hit on fifteen.
Playing like this is no fun.
Hitting on seventeen is an easy bust.
So you can only sit on seventeen...
...and wait to lose.
Hit.
Looks like you...
...still don't have a strong enough hand.
So...
...I still have to rely on...
...Second Uncle's luck in dealing.
Push.
Same points.
But sitting in different seats...
...leads to different outcomes.
The house takes all.
You dare to hit on seventeen?
Aren't you afraid of busting?
It's only seventeen.
If I don't hit...
...am I supposed to just
wait for others to win?
What about you?
Too scared to hit on nineteen?
If I hit again...
...the odds of losing are too high.
So you'd rather lose...
...than take a gamble.
I've never been good at
gambling since I was a kid.
Right.
Ever since you were little, you
weren't cut out for gambling.
You've never been
able to keep your cool.
You don't belong at the gambling table.
Hit me.
You busted.
If you could hold your nerve...
...you might have bet on us both busting.
But now...
Hit.
Stand.
You're standing already?
You stand on nineteen...
...and you're too scared to hit on fifteen.
When will you ever dare to hit?
When my hand is strong enough...
...or when I have no other choice.
Now isn't the time where
you have no other choice.
Blackjack again.
I dealt these cards.
I make the rules.
You don't even dare to hit.
How can you possibly beat me?
You're right, Second Uncle.
The Black Moon Syndicate isn't coming.
I heard...
...someone wants to stab me in the back.
Today's game...
...was just to see...
...who's holding the cards
but is too scared to play them.
Second Uncle.
You don't suspect me, do you?
I've been with you since I was twelve.
I've never disobeyed you in the slightest.
Growing up...
...all these years have been enough time for
you to breed ambition.
Since we're laying it all out...
Second Uncle.
...these are all the men
you have left, right?
A-ren.
Father, go!
You're not worthy...
...to sit at the same table as me.
Kill him.
Brother Yan.
Why are you doing this?
How could you betray Father?
He's not my father.
He raised you.
We're family.
You and I are family.
Lin Cang is not.
A-ren, if you see me as your brother...
...then don't stop me.
Gunshots.
Did the deal go south?
I can't betray Father.
Then I'm sorry.
Lin Yan.
Freeze.
Unless you want to die.
Let me go after Lin Cang.
I'll be too late!
Do you really want to be the next Lin Cang?
No matter who I am...
Lin Cang has to die.
Only when he's dead...
...can things change.
The change I want...
...is for all arms dealers to disappear.
Including Lin Cang.
And including you.
Can you trust me one more time?
Do you think I'd still trust you?
Let me kill Lin Cang...
...and settle all this first.
I'll do whatever you say after that.
Consider it me begging you.
Going after him is a suicide mission.
I have to go.
Otherwise...
...just kill me right now.
A-yan.
If you just come with me now...
...I'll pretend none of this ever happened.
Shut down the whole operation,
and I'll go with you.
A-yan.
So all these years...
...you've hated me this much.
Drop your weapon and surrender.
The government forces are already here.
You can't escape.
Let's test that theory.
I mean no harm.
Daddy...
I finished my mission!
Big brother, you're a good person.
A-ren.
He never...
...considered himself...
...our father.
I will avenge her.